edrugsearch.com 2013-09-23

# Privacy Policy

TRUSTe Certified Privacy

eDrugSearch.com is firmly committed to respecting the privacy of individuals. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

## What This Privacy Policy Covers

This policy covers how eDrugSearch.com treats personal information that eDrugSearch.com collects and receives, including information related to your past use of eDrugSearch.com services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, gender, email address, zip code and that is not otherwise publicly available. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that eDrugSearch.com does not own or control, or to people that eDrugSearch.com does not employ or manage.

eDrugSearch.com has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with TRUSTe's program requirements including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at info@edrugsearch.com.If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact TRUSTe here. 

## Information Collection and Use

### General 

eDrugSearch.com collects personal information when you register with eDrugSearch.com, when you use eDrugSearch.com services, when you visit eDrugSearch.com pages.

When you register we ask for information such as your name, gender, email address, zip code, etc... Once you register with eDrugSearch.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

eDrugSearch.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP, and the page you request.

eDrugSearch.com uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

### Children

Any child under age 18 that attempts to register with eDrugSearch.com, will be asked to leave eDrugSearch.com and their account will be deleted effective immediately.

### Cookies

We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information.

### Third Party Cookies

The use of cookies (session ID and persistent) by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers, etc… is covered by our privacy policy. We do have access or control over these cookies. Our pharmacy partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site, in order for you to use the shopping cart, etc.

Our third party partners employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), images, and scripts that help them better manage content on our site. We do [not] tie the information gathered to our Customers' or Users' personal information. 

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

eDrugSearch.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with eDrugSearch.com under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help eDrugSearch.com communicate with you about offers from eDrugSearch.com and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of eDrugSearch.com's terms of service, or as otherwise required by law.
  * eDrugSearch.com does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.

## Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences 

###  General

You can edit your eDrugSearch.com Member Account Information, at any time.

### Updating/Accessing/Amending/Correcting Personal Information

If your personally information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may [correct, update, amend, delete/remove or deactivate it] by making the change on our member information page [or by emailing our Customer Support at [info@edrugsearch.com](mailto:info@edrugsearch.com) ] or by contacting us by telephone at 210-789-2973 or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the eDrugSearch.com service, such as service announcements and administrative messages that are considered part of your eDrugSearch.com account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. If you no longer wish to receive these emails you can cancel your account by contacting the eDrugSearch.com Site Admin at [info@edrugsearch.com](mailto:info@edrugsearch.com) or you can login click on the “Settings” tab and then click “Delete” account; all your account information will be permanently erased from our servers.

### Choice/Opt-Out

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at [info@edrugsearch.com](mailto:info@edrugsearch.com). To unsubscribe simply login to your account, click on the “Settings” tabs then click on the “Newsletter” tab, and then click on the radio button that states: “No, I do not subscribe to get updates.” Then click on the “Save Settings” button.

### Invite-A-Friend

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. eDrugSearch.com stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

Your friend may contact us at info@edrugsearch.com to request that we remove this information from our database.

### Import Contacts

You can import contacts from your Outlook, Gmail, Yahoo! Mail, Hotmail, AOL, Facebook, LinkedIn, or other email account address book to invite them to become members of our site. We collect the username and password for the email account you wish to import your contacts from and will only use it for that purpose.

### Confidentiality and Security

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [info@edrugsearch.com](mailto:info@edrugsearch.com).

When you enter sensitive information (such as personal health information) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

### Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [info@edrugsearch.com](mailto:info@edrugsearch.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

eDrugSearch.com may update this policy. We will notify you about significant or material changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your eDrugSearch.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

NOTICE: [Click here](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/online/sitesee.htm?__hstc=51977334.26959b9bbf2c72f88429cf90c5c2b37e.1363841925134.1366005730564.1366009651438.20&__hssc=51977334.3.1366009651438) for important information about safe surfing from the Federal Trade Commission.

Effective Date: August 22, 2012

### Links to Other Web Sites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of eDrugSearch.com. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policy. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit.

### Single Sign-On

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

### Social Media Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button [and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

### Public Forums

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [info@edrugsearch.com](mailto:info@edrugsearch.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

### Surveys or Contests

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code).

We use this information to notify contest winners, award prizes, _to monitor site traffic or personalize the site, to send participants an email newsletter._

We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company is prohibited from using our users’ personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

Here is our physical mailing address:  
P.O. Box 1068  
Spring Branch, Texas 78070  
(210) 789-2973

### Message Board Rules and Regulations

To participate in the eDrugSearch.com community, we ask that you follow these requirements:

*  Anyone under the age of 18 must leave this site  
*  No commercial solicitation or affiliate links  
*  No discussion of ongoing or planned criminal activity  
*  No offending, off-topic, cross-posted, misinforming, or insignificant postings  
*  Pharmacies, please introduce yourselves in the New Sources forum

The eDrugSearch.com community is moderated daily by Cary Byrd, the owner of this site, as well as by other employees of eDrugSearch.com whom he designates. Neither Byrd nor any employee of eDrugSearch.com is a medical professional, and our Web site does not provide medical or healthcare advice, diagnosis or treatment.

Additionally, all users of the eDrugSearch.com community should by default be considered non-medical professionals. We encourage all consumers to consult with a physician before deciding to take any medication.

Posts by users of the eDrugSearch.com community are visible to everyone. Users may modify or erase their posts after they are submitted. Community members must post information which is true and correct to their knowledge.

Both users and moderators of the eDrugSearch.com community are required to behave at all times with mutual respect and honesty. Users who use abusive language or otherwise show disrespect or dishonesty will receive a warning; a second instance will result in being banned from the community.
